Please [activate your Author Cats license](https://deborahkingbooks.com/wp-admin/themes.php?page=authorcats-license) to remove this message. Thank you!

### GET YOUR FREE PREQUEL!

Just enter your details below and you'll be the first to know about free giveaways, updates, book release dates, and much more. As a welcome gift you'll receive Your Free Prequel!

I do not sell your data. You can unsubscribe at any time. Read our privacy policy for full details here: https://deborahkingbooks.com/privacy

Terms & Privacy Policy
======================

**We like to keep things simple. No legal jargon!**

This is our simple version of a privacy policy. Below this bit is several pages of more legal ways of putting it, which you’re welcome to read if you have insomnia. Basically, we want you and us to both be happy with how we use your data and if you’re not happy, please let us know: [dk@DeborahKingBooks.com](https://deborahkingbooks.com/privacy-policy/dk@DeborahKingBooks.com).

When you request a free offer from us, we take your first name and email in return. We use this to send you the free offer and we also subscribe you to our regular updates. This contains something nice for you (updates on our books, chances to be an advance reader or book related competitions if any are available). We will add something nice about us and what we are up to (new books coming out, author insights). So you get something nice, and we get the chance to let you know about our future books, which we hope you will enjoy.

We only ever have your email because you agreed we could have it, either via our own website or through a competition’s terms and conditions. Occasionally we receive your data as a hard copy (e.g., at an event) where we add you to the mailing list and then destroy the hard copy (we are not interested in filing cabinets full of email addresses; there isn’t the space in our offices).

You can always unsubscribe from our mailing list any time you’d like to. There’s a link at the bottom with our email. Any problems, email us and we will personally remove your details.

We keep your contact details safely on a respected mailing system (MailChimp). We do not sell your data. We hate it being done to us, so we are not about to do it to you!

This site uses cookies, which pretty much every site in the world does too. The cookies are there to remember things like whether you’ve already subscribed. You can disable your cookies (look it up on your browser help button) but this and other sites may then look or behave weirdly.

That’s it!

Now, here are the 5 extra pages of legal jargon we promised you. Sleep tight.

* * *

Terms & Privacy Policy
======================

### Liberation Publishing Privacy Policy

It is our (Liberation Publishing’s) policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect from you or which you may provide to us, in the circumstances set out below. Accordingly, we have developed this privacy policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate, disclose, safeguard and otherwise make use of your personally identifiable information (“Personal Data”).

We will only collect and use your Personal Data where:

* We have lawful grounds to do so, including to comply with our legal obligations.
* We have legitimate interests in using your Personal Data and your interests and fundamental rights do not override those interests.

For the purposes of the EU General Data Protection Regulation ((EU) 2016/679) (“GDPR”), Liberation Publishing, is the “data controller”. If you have any questions about this policy or about how we use your Personal Data, please contact us via our contact details at the end of this policy.

This policy is effective as of 2018-23-05. We review our privacy practices on an ongoing basis, and as such we may change this privacy policy from time to time. Please check this page frequently to ensure you are familiar with its current content.

##### 1: Personal Data we collect via [DeborahKingBooks.com](https://deborahkingbooks.com/) (the “Website”)

* Personal Data that you provide to us.

We only collect Personal Data where you choose to interact with us on the Website in the following way:

When you sign-up to receive free content, books, including eBooks, and offers, we collect your:

* Email address
* First name

Data that we collect automatically:

We automatically collect certain information when you visit our Website – such as the type of browser and operating system you are using, and the domain name of your Internet service provider. We do not link this information with any Personal Data. We may also collect data automatically through our use of cookies on the Website. Please see the cookie policy (below) to find out about the types of cookies we set and why and how you can adjust your settings to disable cookies.

##### **2: Use of your Personal Data**

We will only use your Personal Data when the law allows us to. Most commonly, we use your Personal Data to:

* Process and manage your use of our website;
* Respond to your questions, comments and requests;
* Where you have opted-in to receive marketing from us, deliver communications that are relevant to your preferences / may be of interest to you;
* Improve our services and Website through analysis of information.

##### 3: Sharing of your Personal Data

We take your privacy seriously and will not share your Personal Data with others, except as permitted by applicable law or as set out below:

We share Personal Data as necessary with third parties who provide services or functions on our behalf and who require the information to provide those specific services to us. These third parties may include social media advertising platforms such as Facebook and Google Adwords for the purpose of custom audience generation and the development of targeting criteria for other audiences. Please note that we have appropriate data privacy safeguards in place with third parties with whom we share Personal Data as described above and who are providing services or functions on our behalf.

##### 4: Keeping your Personal Data secure

We have implemented security policies and technical measures to safeguard the Personal Data we collect. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with applicable US law, to safeguard Personal Data from accidental loss, destruction or damage and unauthorized access, use and disclosure.

##### 5: Retention periods for use of your Personal Data.

We will use and store your Personal Data only for as long as necessary, bearing in mind the uses of your Personal Data as described in this privacy policy and otherwise as communicated to you. We review the Personal Data we hold at regular intervals and delete permanently or anonymize any Personal Data which is no longer necessary.

##### 6: Children

This Website and our services are aimed at adults, and we do not knowingly collect any Personal Data relating to children aged less than 15 years old. If you are under the age of 15, please do not provide any of your Personal Data, including your email address.

##### 7: Access to and control over your Personal Data

You have legal rights under applicable law in relation to your Personal Data. You can ask the following questions, or take the following actions, at any time by contacting us via email or our postal address:

* See what Personal Data we hold about you (if any), including why we are holding it and who it could be disclosed to.
* Ask us to change/correct your Personal Data.
* Ask us to delete your Personal Data.
* Object to the processing of your Personal Data.
* Ask us to restrict the processing of your Personal Data.
* Withdraw any consents you have given us to the processing of your Personal Data.
* Express any concerns you have about third parties’ use of your Personal Data.

##### 8: Change of purpose

We will only use your Personal Data for the purposes for which we collected it, unless we reasonably consider that we need to use it for another reason and that reason is compatible with the original purpose. If you wish to have an explanation as to how the processing for the new purpose is compatible with the original purpose, please contact us. If you need to use your Personal Data for an unrelated purpose, we will notify you and explain the legal basis which allows us to do so

##### **EXTRA: Cookies Policy**

As is common practice with almost all professional websites this site uses cookies, which are tiny files that are downloaded to your computer, to improve your experience.

This page describes what information they gather, how we use it and why we sometimes need to store these cookies. We will also share how you can prevent these cookies from being stored however this may downgrade or ‘break’ certain elements of the site’s functionality.

We use cookies for a variety of reasons detailed below. Unfortunately in most cases there are no industry standard options for disabling cookies without completely disabling the functionality and features they add to this site. It is recommended that you leave on all cookies if you are not sure whether you need them or not in case they are used to provide a service that you use.

##### **Disabling Cookies**

You can prevent the setting of cookies by adjusting the settings on your browser (see your browser Help for how to do this).

Be aware that disabling cookies will affect the functionality of this and many other websites that you visit. Disabling cookies will usually result in also disabling certain functionality and features of the site. Therefore it is recommended that you do not disable cookies.

##### The Cookies We Set

This site offers opt-in up-dates and email subscription services and cookies may be used to remember if you are already registered and whether to show certain notifications which might only be valid to subscribed/unsubscribed users.

When you submit data, cookies may be set to remember your user details for future correspondence.

In some special cases we also use cookies provided by trusted third parties. The following section details which third party cookies you might encounter through this site.

This site is built using WordPress, which uses cookies and also uses Automattic’s Jetpack, which is one of the most widespread and trusted analytics solutions on the web for helping us to understand how you use our site and ways that we can improve your experience. These cookies may track things such as how long you spend on the site and the pages that you visit so we can continue to produce engaging content. For more information on Automattic and WordPress cookies, see the official [Automattic Privacy Notice](https://automattic.com/privacy-notice/), [Automattic Cookie Policy](https://automattic.com/cookies/) and [WordPress Cookie Policy](https://wordpress.org/about/privacy/cookies/) pages.

Third party analytics are used to track and measure usage of this site so that we can continue to produce engaging content. These cookies may track things such as how long you spend on the site or pages you visit which helps us to understand how we can improve the site for you.

From time to time we test new features and make subtle changes to the way that the site is delivered. When we are still testing new features these cookies may be used to ensure that you receive a consistent experience whilst on the site whilst ensuring we understand which optimizations our users appreciate the most.

In some cases we may provide you with custom content based on what you tell us about yourself either directly or indirectly by linking a social media account. These types of cookies simply allow us to provide you with content that we feel may be of interest to you.

We also use social media buttons and/or plugins on this site that allow you to connect with your social network in various ways. For these to work the following social media sites including; Facebook, Instagram, and Pinterest, will set cookies through our site which may be used to enhance your profile on their site or contribute to the data they hold for various purposes outlined in their respective privacy policies.

##### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

**Liberation Publishing**  
15455 Manchester Road, Suite 226  
Ballwin, Missouri 63022-0226  
United States

© Copyright 2018. Last Edited on 2018-06-02.

© Copyright 2024

We are using cookies to give you the best experience on our website.

You can find out more about which cookies we are using or switch them off in settings.

Accept

Close GDPR Cookie Settings

* Privacy Overview
* Strictly Necessary Cookies

Privacy Overview

This website uses cookies so that we can provide you with the best user experience possible. Cookie information is stored in your browser and performs functions such as recognizing you when you return to our website and helping our team to understand which sections of the website you find most interesting and useful.

You can adjust all of your cookie settings by navigating the tabs on the left hand side.

Strictly Necessary Cookies

Strictly Necessary Cookie should be enabled at all times so that we can save your preferences for cookie settings.

Enable or Disable Cookies 

If you disable this cookie, we will not be able to save your preferences. This means that every time you visit this website you will need to enable or disable cookies again.

Enable All Save Changes
